迈克 · 诺斯: 我们接下来要讨论的话题是课程。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: The next topic we're
going to jump into is classes.
您可能熟悉在常规 JavaScript 中使用类。
And you're probably familiar with
using classes in regular JavaScript.
在你已经习惯的基础上增加了一些新的概念。
TypeScript adds some new concepts
on top of what you're used to.
我们需要从阶级领域的角度思考一些新的东西,
There is something new we need to
think about in terms of class fields,
和-TypeScript 还引入了访问修饰符关键字的概念。
and- TypeScript also introduces
the concept of access modifier keywords.
这使我们能够控制谁可以看到成员数据和
Which allow us to have control
over who can see member data and
实例上的成员函数。
member functions on instances.
那么让我们回到音符，回到4-class-basic。 Ts 文件
So let's go to the notes,
to the 4-class-basic.ts file
Mike North: 在这个例子中,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So in this example,
你可以看到一些东西。
you can see a couple things.
首先，我们使用的是我曾经使用过的新东西
The first is that we're using
a new something I've been
要求继承遗产条款，对吗？
calling a heritage clause, right?
扩展是我们唯一可以用来描述从另一个继承的东西
Extends is the only thing that we can
use to describe inheriting from another
你可以说类扩展了基类。
entity in JavaScript,
that you can say class extends base class.
引入了实现，并且
TypeScript introduces implements, and
描述与特定接口对齐的类。
that describes a class aligning
with a particular interface.
所以有电子邮件，我们知道这种类型要求一切都有一个名称
So HasEmail, we know this type
requires that everything have a name
这是一个字符串和一封邮件，这是一个字符串。
that's a string and
an email that's a string.
Mike North: 这对于任何实现这个接口的类来说意味着什么,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: What this means for
any class that implements this interface,
我们必须确保这些属性符合
we have to make sure that these
properties that conform to
这个界面是可用的，并且提前说明了。
that interface are available and
stated upfront.
所以，从这里的意义来说，这就是我们
So, in terms of what this means up here,
this is us
声明这些成员数据字段将存在。
declaring that these member
data fields will exist.
它们的类型是字符串。
And their type is going to be a string.
这里我们说我们接受两个参数
Here we're stating that
we accept two parameters
在构造函数中，我们接受两个参数。
within our constructor,
we accept two parameters.
在这里，我们确保传递构造函数接收到的东西
And down here, we are making sure that we
pass the things our constructor receives
实例，当然就是这个实例，在构造函数中。
onto the instance, which of course
is this, within the constructor.